web4url.com 2011-06-16

# Web4URL Privacy - A Deep Link General Web Directory

**Web4URL** is a highly promoted Deep Links General Web Directory focused on promoting high quality web sites. Because we are a Human Edited Directory, every link sumbited to Web4URL goes through a comprehensive screening to ensure it meets our high standards. 

Click through any of the categories below, or use the search box to find the web site you need. If you are an author of web site, you can add your web site to our directory. We offer Premium and Sponsored listings to help make your site highly visible, which brings more traffic and better placement with search engines. 

What are Deep Links? [Wikipedia](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Deep_link) defines the term as **_"..making a hyperlink that points to a specific page or image on another website, instead of that website's main or home page"_**. This can be benifical if your website contains multiple subjects. Premium and Sponsored listings at Web4URL can have multiple deep links for a single listing.

Dont Forget to add **Web4URL** to your Bookmarks. We are constantly adding new listings each week. You can even add us in your [Del.icio.us Account](http://del.icio.us/post?url=http://www.Web4URL.com/&title=Web4URL%20-%20A%20Deep%20Links%20General%20Directory) or [Google Bookmarks](http://www.google.com/bookmarks/mark?op=edit&output=popup&bkmk=http://www.Web4URL.com&title=Web4URL "Add Web4URL.com to Google Bookmarks")

## Web4URL Privacy Policy

Web4URL.com is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. We take this commitment very seriously. Web4URL wants you to understand how we use the information you provide to us. We believe that you should have the right to approve the use of that information. As technology changes, it may become necessary for Web4URL to make changes to its privacy policy and procedures. All such changes will be posted to this site. To protect your interests, visit this page periodically to review the current terms of our policy. 

**How We Gather Information**

Web4URL.com appreciates and respects the privacy concerns of the visitors to its web site. Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information, name and email. The customer's contact information is used to get in touch with the customer when necessary. This information will not be displayed on our web site. As a general policy, no personal information is automatically collected from customers visiting this web site. However, certain information is recorded as a matter of course by Web4URL.com servers in order to track the number of visitors to the web site and to help provide an enhanced online experience for the visitor. The type of information tracked by our servers includes your computer browser information, operating system and your IP address. Collecting this information allows Web4URL.com to optimize the visitor�s web site experience.

In addition, we use data collection devices such as �cookies�. �Cookies� are small text files a web site can use to recognize repeat users, facilitate the user�s ongoing access to and use of the site and allow a site to track usage behavior and compile aggregate data that will allow content improvements and targeted advertising. Cookies are not programs that come onto a user�s system and damage files. Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to the user that has no meaning outside the assigning site. If a user does not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the user to deny or accept the cookie feature; however, users should note that cookies may be necessary to provide the user with certain features (e.g., customized delivery of information) available on the Web4URL's site.

Web4URL also uses Google and other 3rd party Advertising Networks. Google uses the [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx). This cookie enables Google and other 3rd party advertising networks to serve ads based on your visits to this site and others that you may have visited on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visitng [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**_How We Use this Information_**

Web4URL.com uses personal information for internal purposes only. If you subscribe to the monthly newsletter, Web4URL uses your email address to send you news about or updates to Web4URL's site, and to respond to customer service issues or comments and questions received from you. Upon request, Web4URL will allow any user to �opt out� of further promotional contacts at any time. If you do not wish to receive notification of special offers or news and/or updates to our site(s), please email Web4URL at Admin ( at ) Web4URL ( dot ) com or follow the instructions included in each of our monthly newsletters.

Web4URL reserves the right to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of our sites and to inform advertisers of such information as well as the number of users that have been exposed to or clicked on their advertising banners. Web4URL will provide only aggregated data from these analyses to third parties.

Web4URL reserves the rights to monitor all outgoing e-mails sent from our web site for quality control purposes. All information recieved will be kept strictly confidential.

**_Release of Information When Required_**

Web4URL will release customer information to the appropriate authorities if we are required to do so by law. Web4URL will also release such information if we feel it is necessary in order to protect our rights or the rights of our customers, affiliates, partners, or any other party, and for purposes of protection from fraud and credit risk.

**_Complaint Procedure_**

We take seriously any complaints received by visitors to and users of our site, and attempt to respond to every complaint in a timely fashion. If you have a complaint regarding our site, materials contained on our site, inappropriate behavior or postings by other users of the site, or otherwise concerning our site or visitors and/or users of our site. You may submit your complaint to us by emailing our Customer Service representatives at Admin ( at ) Web4URL ( dot ) com. Please use the word �Complaint� in the subject line, and include the following information in your email:

  * Your name, address and, if you are a subscriber, your user ID;
  * The basis of your complaint;
  * If your complaint concerns the activities of other users/visitors to the site, the specific type of inappropriate or offensive behavior engaged in or materials posted and, insofar as possible, the identity of the offending user/visitor;
  * The date(s) such behavior occurred or such materials were posted.

A Customer Service representative will respond to your email within 1 day of its receipt and if, in Web4URL determination, your complaint is a valid one, Web4URL will within a reasonable time period take action to deal with the circumstances from which the complaint arose.

**_Security_**

Web4URL implements industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

**_How to Contact Us_**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us at Admin ( at ) Web4URL ( dot ) com. Any dispute arising between you and Web4URL with respect to privacy is subject to the terms and conditions of use and this privacy statement, including limitations on damages, arbitration, and application of the laws of the state of New Jersey in the United States of America.

The foregoing policies are effective as of December 1, 2007. Web4URL reserves the right to change this policy at any time. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.
